Today's live lesson
First, we need to adjust the video.
Now I'm using a world coordinate, so I can switch this world coordinate at the 3D window.
If you adjust a lot of small panels, it will move a lot of angles, which is inconvenient.
So switching the world coordinates, it is based on the environment.
It will not adjust its coordinates according to the movement of the coordinates, which makes it easier for us to operate.
Then we can arrange the panels that need to be divided a little closer.
Then adjust the other panels a little closer.
Then if we overlap, we also select the weight and move it over.
Then arrange its level.
Then the back panels are the same.
Let's put it down a little bit.
Then open the arrangement point.
Then there are layers of panels that must be selected all together.
Then if the position is too high, you can adjust the X and Y axis and the radius of the X and Y axis at the right window.
Then adjust the X and Y axis and the radius of the X and Y axis at the right window.
Then adjust the Y and the Y axis at the right window.
For a position adjustment.
Then we adjust the Y axis a little bit here.
Let it move down a little bit.
Then we also choose all the panels on the back.
Then arrange the back up.
Here we can select the top panel and then use the quick arrangement tool to click on the panel and then quickly arrange it to the top.
Then we adjust it a little bit.
Let's put it on top of it.
Then the bottom one is also arranged.
Then we can select all the small panels that are not arranged.
Then there is the shoulder strap at the back.
We select it and then activate it.
Here, the panel is relatively small.
You can freeze it and activate it.
Then choose to activate it here.
Then take a look.
Next, we want to
make a cut of a panel.
Because these panels are symmetrical on both sides.
So we cut it off.
Then select the base line first.
We select all these base lines.
Because this is an internal line that I made in advance.
We select and then right-click to cut it.
Then we select all the panels that are cut in these simple ways.
Then we don't want this one.
Then right-click on the panel and make a symmetrical panel.
A link between the panel and the fennel line.
Then it is linked to a blue color.
A color of the outer frame.
Then the next is the fennel.
Then you can take a look at it.
Let's first sew all the front pieces together.
And then this side is from the top, and then press it with the free sewing machine, and then press the shift key.
You can do a lot of sewing with one stroke.
And then I'm going to put it on the bottom.
And then there's the zipper on this side, and I'm going to sew it up on both sides.
And then we're going to fix it here.
And then the next thing we're going to do is we're going to fix it here.
And then the next thing we're going to do is we're going to fix it on the edge of the bag.
And then here we can use a tool that only has a sewing line on the outside of the 2D or 3D version of the mouse to move it on the outside of the version to determine its direction or starting point.
In this way, we can know where to start sewing.
In this way, it's not easy to make mistakes.
And then here we see it from the top.
I'm going to sew it down.
And then this side is also from this side down and sew it to this black spot.
And then it's the same at the bottom.
We can move it according to the previous method and see where it is.
And then we're going to do a survey.
And then in 3D, you can also hit a view that you can see and then do a survey.
And then take a look.
I just saw a question.
understanding,
What kind of situation does card support require?
Now card support, for example, for larger boards.
You can use card support for a card support program that can provide the Champion to my device for a card support according to design is portability and debts only from buying a mouse because it can't make music.
If the board is relatively small, you can do a freeze, because if it is frozen, it is equivalent to this board does not exist, it does not participate in the simulation, if it is frozen, it is equivalent to this board exists in this 3D window, and then it is also involved in the simulation, which will affect a little simulation speed.
If the board is relatively small, it doesn't matter if both are frozen and anti-activated, and then we go to the back of the board and put it on the back of the board, and then we go down to the bottom.
Let's take a look.
And then there's the bottom here.
We put it in a view that can be seen, and then we do a test.
And then let's take a look at the side.
No.
We can sew a long line first, then a short line.
You can do a multi-stage analysis with the shift key.
Because there has been a link before, so just sew one side.
This is a zipper, sew it up.
Then let's take a look.
Let's see where there is no sewing.
And then I see there are two small triangles in the back.
We select it and then move it out.
We don't powder it first.
We'll sew it later.
And then turn it off.
And then the back piece, we select all of them and then freeze it.
This is to simulate.
Wait a minute.
Put its shape on the support.
And then now we're going to put this on before we simulate it.
For the time being.
This way, if you simulate it, its shape will look better.
It won't be very soft.
I'll simulate it.
And then you can see that the fabric is still a little soft.
Next, we can add a fabric.
We find the fabric.
And then drag it into the fabric.
And then we increase the quality.
And because this version is relatively small, I can directly increase it to five.
Its simulation speed will not affect much.
And if the version is more complicated, you can stand at about eight.
And here, I'll change it to five.
And then the other parameters can be confirmed directly.
And then after you've adjusted it, you can just do a simulation.
Then we still have to adjust its shape a little bit.
Pull it a little bit to make it look better.
Here, for the tutorial, I'll just do the same thing as before.
OK, let's adjust it.
I saw that there was a problem with the front and back of the three-piece version.
How do you stand up?
Did you freeze the back before the simulation?
Then the simulation will not collapse.
You can use the freeze to make the back panel.
You can see.
And now I'm going to untangle the back.
And then because there's a little hole.
And then we'll simulate it.
Just simulate it a little bit.
The freeze in the front here is to keep it in shape.
Don't fall down.
Because the back is not untangled.
And then it's a process.
For example, there are some boxes.
This gap in the back is dug in.
And then we can use the ferrite line to make a adjustment.
We choose the ferrite line.
And then in the vertical angle on the right.
Adjust it to more than 180 degrees.
It can go in and out.
Go in and out.
We can adjust it to 260 degrees here.
And then you can simulate it here.
Look at the effect.
Make a adjustment.
And then we're going to do an internal line.
And then here.
The internal line is what I've done before.
If you want to do it.
You can just use the internal line to adjust it.
Four or five millimeters is fine.
I'll hook it up here.
Because I've already prepared it in advance.
And then select the internal line.
Select the basic line.
And then hook it up to the internal line.
And then we're going to select these internal lines.
And then make a setting of its angle.
And then the back of the internal line.
And then turn off one of his direct rendering.
If you don't turn it off.
He'll have a corner.
It's not very good.
And then this angle.
It's small.
Just adjust it to 120.
And then simulate it.
Look at one of its effects.
You can see it.
It's the place of the grave.
It's an effect of digging into it.
And then the other shoes.
And then adjust it a little bit.
And then there's a little bit of a hole in the back.
And then pull it a little bit to the side.
And then we're going to freeze it.
And then the front one.
We need to adjust one of the effects in front of us.
It's also here, then we put it in the grave.
It's also to find the grave line.
The grave line.
The corresponding grave line.
Select the corresponding
Then change the right angle to
Then adjust the value to see the effect
Then hook all the internal lines
We select all the internal lines
Then right click hook as
Then we need to adjust its angle
We select the internal line
All selection
Then turn off the direct rendering
The direct angle is changed to about 120
Then we don't need to be too rough
We adjust to 150
Adjust the effect
Then we can simulate
You can see its effect
Then these places can also be simulated
Then pull it to make it look better
Look at it
And then we have some small panels that are not divided
Then we can freeze some of the panels in front first
Then select the small panels that are not divided
Then we can pull it down
Or use that quick arrangement
Arrange it to one near it
Then do a analysis
Then here I will directly use it to locate the ball
Then put it near the panel that needs analysis
Pull it out a little bit
Then the other side
Then rotate it a little bit
Pull it down a little bit
Then we use free feng shui line
You can also see where it is
Then hit a place where you can see the feng shui line
Here you can see
Let's wait a little bit
I see there is a problem
Is the hardware version of India the same?
Will it be affected by the parameters of the material
Hardware hardware is currently the same
Let's put it here first
Then put it on the other side
Then the other side is the same
Let's go to the back
Then look at it
Where is the starting point of a feng shui line
It's on the top
This one
Then divide it into this point of reference
That's it
Then there's the bottom one
We don't have it yet
We need to hook its base line as the inner line
Then just sew these two pieces together
Then we sew it
We can remove this version and select hardening
Then
Control plus H to remove hardening
Then simulate again
Because this side doesn't need to be very hard
version
And then I'm going to make a mirror
So this is how I do it
Cut it off
Then select the middle panel
At this double-click point
Active center point
Then move one side
It will move both sides at the same time
Move at the same time
Right click
It will pop up a dialogue frame
We enter the value
Then make sure that it can be shortened both ways simultaneously
Ok!
Then we add a layer to make it a little harder, and then we can simulate it to see the effect.
Well, if it's almost done, then we put it in the back.
There are two small triangles.
We also sewed it up.
Triangles.
And then he started from this point and then sewed it up.
And then I'm going to change it because it's going to be a little bit more stable.
And then we choose it.
And then move it a little bit closer to the board to make it a little bit more stable.
And then you can simulate it after you've adjusted it.
There's another one.
It's one of the front pieces that's not sewed.
I sewed the front piece before the belt.
Let's merge them.
And then we'll merge the bottom one.
After that, we can hook the base line right in the middle.
I'm going to do it.
We can use the SHIFT key to select more, and then select the middle one, and then the right key to create a pattern for the inner line.
In the case of G9, we can lock all the panels and then select the inner line, the base line, and then create the inner line, and quickly create it.
And then we do the analysis.
I'm going to sew these lines one by one.
I'm going to sew them one by one.
And then there are two lines in the front and two in the back.
Before we sew, we need to remove all the outer parts of the panel.
First, remove it, and then sew it.
And then here, the pattern of the sewing line has to be changed to TEND, because it needs to overlap the sewing line.
And then the bottom is the same.
Sew it up.
And then the pattern of the sewing line has also been changed to TEND.
And then this panel is a little far away.
We can untie it first, and then right-click it and add it to the outside.
At this time, we can see that it is relatively flat.
All we have to do is simulation.
It will look better.
And, let's select this design.
button.
Let's untangle it first.
Then we need to combine the back pieces.
We need to clone a back piece.
Combine it.
Before cloning, we need to cut the base line into the inner line.
After the cloning, the inner line will automatically be cut.
We don't need to manually cut it later.
Then we clone it from the outside.
Then put it down.
It's already cloned from the outside.
Cloned a back piece.
Next, add pressure.
Add a positive pressure on the outer plate.
Add a negative pressure on the inner plate.
The model will bulge.
This effect mainly shows the effect of adding cotton.
Let's see.
Let's look at the back and see the effect.
You can see that it slowly bulges in the back.
It shows a kind of cotton effect.
After the cloning, we can freeze it.
Then we do some other operations.
Let's untangle the front first.
Then the hardening is not needed.
Then you can see that it only has one material now.
We can now add some other materials.
Then we can add some other materials.
There are some details here.
Because there is a fabric on this side.
There is a zipper at the bottom.
So I cut it off.
Cut it open.
In this way, it will be easier to add the material later.
Then now we add a material.
Now we add a material.
In this way, it will be easier to你的
Then this is a belt.
We found two side abutors.
Apply it to it.
Then pull it over,
It is a fabric from the back mesh.
Take it off.
lemme
We can untangle it first and then see the effect.
There's a little bit of it in the back.
Let's add other fabrics first.
Let's add the fabric at the bottom first.
To add these, we need to put some of the previously cut fabrics together.
In this way, you don't have to choose only one piece of fabric.
You don't need to choose more pieces of fabric.
And then put these together.
And then there's a chain of fabric on top.
Let's right-click and merge.
After merging, we can add more fabrics.
And then apply the fabric at the bottom.
And then the chain of fabric.
And then select the chain of fabric.
And then there are two more to select.
And then the chain of fabric.
And then apply it.
For the chain of fabric, we need to adjust the texture here.
We can switch the texture surface.
And then use the editor texture tool to pull the texture of the chain a little bit.
To make the effect more realistic.
On the other side, I copied a new fabric.
And then apply a chain.
And then here, you can actually do it directly.
You don't have to copy a new fabric.
You can directly use this.
Adjust it at the end of the chain.
On this side, I copied a fabric.
And then make a texture adjustment.
And then there's a belt.
Let's apply a new fabric to the front belt.
And then we can slightly enlarge its thickness.
And then there are two puerta next to it.
Here's the little triangle.
We can slightly enlarge its thickness by choosing the thickness a little bit.
About 0.5.
A little bit thicker.
And then put it on the belt.
Put the belt on the belt.
Put the belt here.
And then we select all the panels, because now it's a little crooked, let's hit it a little bit, hit it a little bit.
And then we freeze it on top, and then we adjust the simulation a little bit below.
Adjust the bottom a little bit.
Wait a minute, and then we can choose to freeze it all, because if we do it in the front, we can freeze it and then move it up.
At this time, we need to make a shoulder strap at the back, because the shoulder strap is longer and it will stick to the ground, so we move it up and leave the grid surface.
And then you can see below.
Because I was just at the grid surface.
If it's not easy to operate, you can move these two panels now.
Freeze these two panels.
You can see that it's a little bit uneven below.
And then we deal with it.
Let's take a look at the internal line.
This is the ferrite line.
Let's take a look.
The internal line is not processed here.
Let's hook it up first.
Hook up the internal line.
And then wait a minute.
And then change it to 120 degrees.
And then the bottom one is also hooked up to the internal line.
And then turn off the shoulder strap directly.
Change the angle to 120.
Here you can also adjust it according to the effect.
Then simulate.
You can see that its shape will gradually become better.
It's a little bit better.
And then take a look.
And then we put it in the back.
Then there's a band behind it.
We hooked it up to a plate.
Make a band.
Then we can delete this internal line.
We don't need it.
Just delete it.
And then there's half of it here.
We can just open it.
Open it.
And then sew it up.
Sew it up on both sides.
And then the bottom one is also fixed.
The bottom one needs to be changed to TEN.
Because it needs to be a little flat.
And then there are two sides.
It's the same.
Change the internal line.
Then it's also changed to TEN.
And then select the plate.
It's a little far now.
We can add it directly to the outside.
And you'll see that the plate of our Kron here has a relatively large vertical diameter.
We can adjust it a little bit.
Adjust to 5.
Then.
And then the speed of the collision can also be reduced a little bit.
And then we can freeze the other ones that we don't simulate.
And then simulate.
You can take a look.
And then if the front is done, we can deal with the back of this one.
We can quickly arrange it to the back of the bag.
Pull it out a little bit.
Then I'm going to turn it around here.
To a
Face us on the front.
In fact, you can also do it on the right side of the board.
a
Turn the water bottle over.
And then we're going to put a piece of tape on this side.
Put it next to the one that needs to be painted.
And then I'm going to sew it up.
And then I'm going to sew it up here.
And then I'm going to harden it.
Harden it.
And then I'm going to open the simulation.
It's very stable.
And then I'm going to put it on the back of the bag.
I think it's fairly stable.
It's very stable.
Let's try to do it.
And we can use the back of the bag as a little stand in the middle of the box.
It's very stable.
And then we're going to use that on the back.
And then we'll add some other tape to it.
All the internal lines, then hook it up to the internal line.
Then we select the version, right-click, and then do a colon.
Outer, colon to outer.
The effect of the colon here may not be very obvious if you use pressure.
The following method is to make it in a way that increases the thickness and conflicts.
For example, let's add 5 first and see the effect.
If you don't think you can, you can make it a little bigger.
You can take a look at the effect.
I added 8 here.
You can see the effect of it.
Then after adding it, we freeze it.
At this time, we can reduce the conflict a little bit.
Because we need to analyze some other versions.
If the conflict is bigger, it will simulate instability.
The smart version must be frozen, otherwise it will transform.
The simulation will transform.
Then we hook up this small version.
Then quickly arrange the circumference of the version it needs to be sewed.
Pull it out a little bit.
Let me adjust it.
Then just do a sewing.
Just sew it up.
Let's sew it all up the other side.
Then eagle.
Then simulation.
The fast cut of the hardening is CCLK so H.
And then here we can use the folding arrangement tool.
Fold it up and sew it on both sides.
And then simulate.
We don't need the inner thread here.
We can just delete it and make it smoother.
And then we can make it smaller.
Because this version is smaller.
The effect is not very big.
Make it smaller.
And then simulate.
It will be very natural.
Pull it out a little bit.
And then simulate.
And then here.
My thickness has increased.
I'm going to increase the thickness.
I'm going to make it bigger.
Because the effect will be better.
And then adjust it.
And then the following is to draw.
We first lock all the outer frames of the board.
And then hook it out of the inner thread of this band.
And then undo it.
And then sew the band on it.
And then sew it down.
And then use the free sewing line to sew the top section.
And then we can add it to the outside directly.
And then just simulate it.
And then here we can make the middle one a little bit bigger and then you can see that it will have that kind of feeling that it is opened.
You can see its effect.
Pull this one.
Then this one is done, we need to make a bullet at the bottom.
We arrange it quickly to the bottom and then adjust it a little bit with the locator.
Adjust the position.
Pull it a little bit.
If you pull it, it will be more stable to simulate.
We look at a spring line and then find the triangle.
Then put it here.
Then I'm going to print this board and then simulate it.
We can untie this triangle and participate in the simulation.
Make it work better.
And then at the bottom, we need to add a row of pins.
And then we double-click that triangle.
You can add a row of pins with a double-click.
And then after this pin is added, we open the simulation.
And then in the simulation, select it and use the locator to move it to the area where you need to wear a wooden buckle.
Let's zoom in a little bit here.
This.
If you need to adjust it slowly.
Move it around.
Let's move it around.
Then let's move it slowly.
This.
Here.
If you can use other methods, you can also add an inner line and fold it over, which method is more convenient.
Then I'll move it over here.
Then we select the center and adjust it a little bit closer to it, but you don't need to be very close to it.
We'll put it next to it a little bit, because we're going to add a secondary key later.
Then adjust it again.
Let's pull it a little bit.
Then this position is actually almost the same.
Then we add a secondary key.
Just put this double key in.
Then here, if we import this secondary key, we import it as a secondary key.
Choose to add and then import it as a secondary key.
Then confirm.
Wait a minute.
Then we use this glue to stick it to this secondary key.
Adjust it a little bit.
Then you can see that this secondary key is a little different from the real secondary key.
Some of its bands have become a secondary key.
That's because we're going to put this band in.
As long as you put the upper band in.
As long as you put the lower band in.
Just the one with the fixing pin.
Just put the two nearby bands together.
Make it look like a band.
In this way, it will be much more convenient to operate.
Okay, I'll put it here.
Adjust it up there.
Let's freeze it.
Then open the model below.
Let's adjust this band a little bit.
Put it a little bit in line with the band near it.
Make it look better.
It's like making a fake band.
Then here, maybe you need to adjust it a little bit.
Then adjust it up a little bit.
Okay, let's close it.
And then we can just sew the two bands here.
And then it's going to be a tent.
And then we're going to move it over.
Put it in.
Near a template that needs to be simulated.
Because it's a floating tent.
So if you simulate it, it's not going to be very open.
It's going to overlap slowly.
And then pull it a little bit.
Adjust its shape a little bit.
And then it's like this.
Half of the band behind this is done.
So if you need something else, you can add it in slowly.
For example, there are other bands behind it.
You can add them all.
Then apply a fabric to a fabric of a band.
And then.
And then in the back.
We need to unhook the column first.
Unhook the column first.
And then unhook the column first.
And then select.
Select all.
You can do a copy.
And then copy it.
We select all.
Use the positioning ball to move it.
Move it to the other side of the bag.
Make it a little bit better.
Let's zoom in.
And then the position.
Adjust it a little bit.
You can see that there's a overlap here.
We can reverse activate this version.
And then do a simulation.
And then adjust the shoulder strap a little bit.
Pull it out a little bit.
And then simulate it a little bit.
And then pull it out a little bit.
Because the reverse activation is equivalent to this version does not exist.
And then freeze it.
And then simulate it.
It won't penetrate.
And then let's adjust it a little bit.
And then sew the top strap to the edge of the bag.
I'll simulate it here first.
Let's adjust this component first.
Because of the component.
The other side has been adjusted to a position before.
If the component is attached here.
Just adjust it.
It's fast.
Because the previous version was on the other side.
I've simulated a position.
So just adjust it a little bit.
Just adjust it a little bit.
And then the belt on the top.
Sew it to the bag.
Fix it.
And then sew it up.
At this point, we need to put that.
We select the two panels of the sponge.
Solve it.
Let it simulate.
Here, as long as the quick simulation is stopped.
Because it needs to conflict.
If it is simulated for a long time, it will be flat.
And then stop it.
And then it's a bag on the top.
The bag on the top.
Let's quickly arrange it first.
A copy of it.
And then move it up a little bit.
And then I put it.
The board is a little flat.
And the ground is a little bit flat.
And then add a fixing pin.
And then it's sewed.
Don't sew it wrong.
It's okay.
And then sew it up.
Okay, the other side.
Sew it up.
And then at this point, if it's simulated.
It will make the pattern of the bag itself.
That shape.
Okay, let's pause here.
I didn't freeze the bag just now.
If this is simulated.
If you raise your hand.
You need to freeze the shoulder strap.
Otherwise, the shape will change.
And then freeze it first.
And then simulate it again.
And then we also put this shoulder strap.
A band of this hand.
Make it a little thicker.
And then take a look.
Turn off this inner line and base line display.
And then add some details.
If you wrap this bag.
It's done.
The details are generally done.
You can add some details.
For example, I add a zipper here.
Choose to add.
And then pour it in.
Confirm.
And then put it in.
And then if you add it.
We'll just put it in the zipper.
That position is fine.
It's just a little bit better when you put it in.
Just a little bit better when you put it in.
But this bag.
You don't have to simulate it.
You don't have to add it nearby.
And then we'll make it a little bigger.
Make it a little bigger.
Adjust it a little bit.
Pull it out a little bit.
And then one of its types should be changed to metal.
And then the zipper is good.
And then I'll add another zipper.
And then then we'll make it a little bit bigger.
Find the zipper.
Added another zipper.
And then I'll put it in.
Confirm.
Then we'll make it quickly with the glue.
In the vicinity of the zipper.
And then adjust the position.
I also did this zipper with the sheet.
There was an additional design in my live broadcast.
You can take a look.
Then let's adjust it a little bit.
Let's pull it out.
Well, this one needs to be adjusted a little bit.
If you think it's too big, you can adjust it a little bit smaller on this side, and you can adjust it on the right side, and then you can put it in place a little bit.
We can change its type separately.
Change this ring to a metal one.
Well, this bag is generally done.
I'm not going to add the other accessories one by one.
Well, for example, there's a name line.
You can add anything here.
Then we choose a fabric.
A mesh fabric on both sides of the bag.
Drag it in and select it.
Then apply this mesh cloth.
And then the bag is generally done.
And then this is a bag I've done before.
You can take a look at the effect.